DUONG THỊ ANH KHOA

MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

Objective

Take advantages of sale/marketing skills, medical information and understanding oftender to become a professional MR (Medical Representative) then a MAS (Market Access Specialist) and bring more value to customers. From that, I will contribute to development of the company.



Education

VO TRUONG TOAN UNIVERSITY

2011 - 2016

Faculty of Pharmacy

GPA: 3.1/4 (Good)



Work Experience

DHA CORPORATION

JULY 2017 - PRESENT

Market Access Executive (Sale and Marketing)

- Do product presentation to convince and establish privileged relations with target Health Operators in order to achieve sales
- Promote and sell company's products to target audiences based on action plan and marketing plan
- Establish & maintain close relationship with key accounts through ensuring company services meet their requirements
- Event management the coordination and implementation of internal, external events
- Handle all stages of market access campaign

MERCK EXPORTGMBH

MAY 2017 - JULY 2017

Market Access and Pricing (MAP) Assistant (LEAVE DUE TO PARENTS'SICK)

- Event management the coordination and implementation of internal, external events
- Supports the PM Marketing Team, MAP -Manager in the execution of the RO-PU Operational Plan and in the administrative tasks of the department.

ZUELLIG PHARMA

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY

2017

Hospital Sales Consultant

Handle all the stages of the tender processes, contract (tender, direct purchase, priceapplication). Good relationship with Pharmacy Department of Hospitals and staffs: Pediatric Hospital 2, Binh Tan Hospital, City Hospital, Trieu An Hospital... and someother private hospitals as well as clinics

- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries directly or via phone and email.
- Help supply goods in time through supporting paperworks, placing and monitoring orders, solving problems.
- Collect market information, customers' feedback, tender...



-TOEIC Certificate with score 800/990

2016



- (iii) 27th November, 1992
- 🛂 Female
- **Q** 0933 967 902
- 🔳 khoa2711@gmail.com
- Phone (Vietnam)

INTERESTS

- Learn new things
- Music and travel

SKILLS

Co-operation

Communication and negotiation

English Speaking

Work under high-pressure

Fast learn